Hello friend welcome to Stock Research Center.
Today we are going to talk about the
stock of ICICI Lamborgh General Insurance Company.  The
company's quarter two
results have come here and the
company's numbers are in
front of you.  This value given here is
given in lax.  We will
convert this into crores and
show you the number.  The
total income from operations in
this quarter was around Rs 6582 crore.
Last quarter it was Rs 683 crore
and in the same quarter last year it was Rs 5850
crore.  Now there is income.
After income, the expenses are also incurred by the company here.
So the total expenses, the total costs, are
given in section number 12.
5830 crores have been made this quarter.  Last
quarter Rs 5000
429 crore, in the same quarter of last year Rs
86 crore, so the expenses are also
continuously increasing here on
quarter on quarter basis and year on
year basis.  Ok?  Just as income has increased on a
quarter-on-quarter and year-on-year basis,
expenses have also increased here.
Now let us talk about operating profit.
Operating Profit: If you look here, the
operating profit section has
come to around Rs 752 crore.  And in the last quarter it came
here to around Rs 654 crore.
In the same quarter of last year it was around Rs 664 crore.  Let's
talk about taxes first.
If we talk about after tax then you will go down
here.  Profit after
tax will be PAT after tax.  PAT will be
in section number 27.  You
can see how much this has come here, 819 crores and 747 crores
in the last quarter and
693 crores in the same quarter of last year, so the tax has also increased
after tax, you can see this,
sorry profit has increased after tax here on
Q on Q basis and year on year
basis, so according to us the company has
shown positive numbers.  You
can tell us how you liked the number by commenting in the comment box.  If you
like the video,
please like the video.  Subscribe to the newly created channel on the channel.
Also turn on the bell
notification.  See you
in the next video.